manymo.com 2013-05-06

# - 1 -

Manymo Privacy Policy
This Manymo Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) states the privacy practices and policies that
apply to the Manymo website and software application located at app.manymo.com (the
“Service”). The Service is owned and operated by Manymo, LLC (referred to as “Manymo,”
“we,” and “our”) and its licensors. This Privacy Policy applies to all visitors to and registered
users (the “user,” “you,” and “your”) of the Service.
Your privacy matters to us, so please take the time to read this Privacy Policy carefully.
Accessing and using the Service constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. We reserve
the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time in our sole discretion. We will provide users
and visitors with a notice of such changes posted on the Service itself. Your continued use of the
Service following the posting of any changes to this Privacy Policy means that you accept and
agree to the changes.
This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect, why we collect it, how we use the
information, and your choices for restricting the use of this information.
Information You Provide Us
We collect personal information directly from you so that you can establish an account and we
can provide the Service to you. This information includes your name, an email address and, if
you purchase a subscription, may include credit card information. We will only use this
information to manage your account and provide you with the Service unless you give us express
permission to use it for another purpose.
We do not store or process your credit information using our own systems. We contract with
online credit card processing services for all our payment transactions. For the name of our
current credit card processing service and information on their security standards please contact
us at support@manymo.com.
When you contact us via email or any other means, we may keep and use a record of that
communication indefinitely to address issues with the Service or for any other business purpose.
We may use your email address to contact you about changes to the Service or this Privacy
Policy.
Information We Collect from Your Use of the Service
We may use the following methods to collect information as you use the Service:
Log Information- When you use the Service we may automatically collect and store certain
information in server logs, such as IP addresses, hardware settings, browser type, and referring
URLs.
                                                 -1-

Local Storage- We may collect and store information locally on the device you use to access the
Service, such as in web browser storage and application data caches.
Cookies and Other Identifiers- We use various technologies to collect and store information
when you visit the Service, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous
identifiers to your device. You may set your web browser to limit or block cookies. If you do so,
the Service may not function properly for you.
We use all the information that we collect as you use the Service to operate, maintain, protect,
improve, and enhance the Service and your user experience. We will ask your consent before
using this information for any other purpose.
Information We Provide to Others
We do not share your personal information with any third parties unless one of the following
applies:
We Have Your Consent- We may share personal information with third parties when we have
your consent to do so. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any personally identifiable
information.
With Account Administrators- If you are using the Service pursuant to a “Master User
Agreement,” as defined in the Manymo User Agreement, then an account administrator may
have access to your account information. This may include your username, email address, and
other personal information. The person or legal entity with whom we are a party to the Master
User Agreement is responsible for establishing a policy for handling this account information.
For External Processing or Storage- We may provide your personal information to our network
and computer infrastructure contractors to store or process it for us, based on our instructions and
in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security
measures.
For Legal Reasons- We may share your personal information with third parties if we determine
that disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to: meet any applicable law or
regulation, or comply with any legal process; investigate potential claims and enforce this
Privacy Policy or the Manymo User Agreement; address fraud, security, or technical issues; or
protect against harm to the rights, property, or safety of Manymo, our users, or the public as
required or permitted by law.
Upon a Sale of the Business- We may transfer your information to a third party as part of a
merger, reorganization, acquisition, or business asset sale. If we do, we will ensure that your
personally identifiable information remains confidential.
                                                 -2-

Application of this Policy
This Privacy Policy only applies to the Service. It does not apply to any websites or software
applications owned or operated by any third parties, including any websites with links from our
Service. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Service, and to read the privacy
statements of each website that collects personal information from you.
Data Security
Access to your personally identifiable information and all the data you store on the Service is
limited to authorized Manymo personnel and is restricted by password protection and other
security mechanisms. Although total security does not exist on the Internet, we will make
commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard all the information that you submit us.
Changes
We may change this Privacy Policy periodically. We will not reduce your rights under this
Privacy Policy without your explicit consent.
Contacting Us
If you have questions or concerns about our practices or this Privacy Policy, please send an email
to support@manymo.com.
Last revised: April 24, 2013.
Copyright 2013 © Manymo, LLC All rights reserved.
                                               -3-
